Let the Fur Fly!
Garfield's Pet Force is a family, comedy, adventure
film directed by Mark A.Z. Dippé.
Nothing in the world can make Garfield get involved in anything besides eating, until the muscular super cat
Garzooka comes crashing into Cartoon World from the Comic Book universe with terrifying news.
Garfield summons up the willpower to join his superhero
Garzooka in a fight to save their worlds.
Garfield / Garzooka / Narrator (voice), played by Frank Welker.
Vetvix (voice), played by Vanessa Marshall.
Odie / Odious (voice), played by Gregg Berger.
Jon Arbuckle / Emperor Jon (voice), played by Wally Wingert.
Arlene / Starlena (voice), played by Audrey Wasilewski.
Nermal / Abnermal (voice), played by Jason Marsden.
Garfield's Pet Force is a 2009 American animated superhero comedy film based on characters from
the Jim Davis comic strip Garfield and loosely based on the Pet Force novel series.
It is the third installment of the animated movie series,
following Garfield Gets Real and Garfield's Fun Fest.
Also, it is the fifth Garfield movie overall.
It was released on DVD and Blu-ray Disc in the United States on June 16, 2009, by 20th Century Fox Home
Entertainment, while it was pre-sold overseas by sales representative Velvet Octopus.
It was written by Garfield creator Jim Davis.
It was released theatrically in 3-D in select countries such as Poland, Italy, Mexico and
Spain, and became the most profitable film in the franchise until 2024.
It is the last Garfield film to be distributed by 20th Century Fox (who lost the film and television rights to the
Garfield franchise shortly after the film's release), ten years prior to Nickelodeon's acquisition of Paws, Inc.
in August 2019.
A sixth film, The Garfield Movie, was released in May 2024.
It was distributed by Sony Pictures Releasing
under their Columbia Pictures label.
The film explores themes of cat, cartoon, villain, surrealism, based on comic.
The tone is lighthearted and mind_bending.